Register of the T. V. (Tzu-wen) Soong papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Material Opened in 2008, 1944
  - Memorandum concerning the politico-military situation in China, 1944 October 26
    Box/Folder 64: 8. Notated in handwriting, "General Chennault's memorandum, discovered among his effects after his death and handed to me by Thomas G. Corcoran on Wednesday, October 14, 1959, after a luncheon at Baroque. T. V. Soong" (from box 37, T. V. Soong papers)
- Scrapbook containing copies of invoices, correspondence, receipts, primarily from the Bank of China, Shanghai, 1937-1938 (Reel 80)
  Box 65. Previously in box 40 (with other oversize material).
- Silk banner, "Efficient Government, Harmonious People" (Anti-communist banner of Qingyuan County, Guangdong Provincial Government), undated (Box Preservation)
- Declassified U.S. Government Records, 1942-1943
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover, thereunder chronologically by date of creation.
  - 2016 February release of records, 1942-1943 (Map case)
    Consists of the following four maps: Burma-Yunnan Borderlands, 1942; Kuang-chou [Guangzhou] (Canton), China, 1943; K'un-ming [Kunming] (Yunnanfu), East, 1943; and Pei-ping [Beiping] (Peking), 1943.
  - 2017 Release of records, 1940-1945 (Reading room workstation)